A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Second Auditor - Literary Fund Records, 1785-1927
Library of Virginia
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 301-320, 1857 April-May (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 321-336, 1857 June-July (Box 24, Folder 7)
- White tithables, 1856, 1861 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Oversize, Abstracts of school operations, 1861-1862 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Oversize, Accounts with John Preston to purchase stock, 1829 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Oversize, Accounts, 1905-1912 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Albemarle County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Botetourt County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Goochland County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Hanover County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Nansemond County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Nicholas County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Norfolk), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Powhatan County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Princess Anne County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Lists of fines and penalties (Wythe County), 1810-1822 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oversize, Receipts, 1857 (Box 25, Folder 5)